New York State Common Cause; Records apap059
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Lobbying Files, 1976-1987; 3; 0.5 cubic ft.
  - Hobday, et. al., v. New York Temporary State Commission on Regulation of Lobbying (Folder 1), 1980 (Box 6 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 48)
  - Hobday, et. al., v. New York Temporary Commission on Regulation of Lobbying (Folder 2), 1980 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 1)
  - Lobbying Assignments, 1976 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 2)
  - Lobbying Assignments, 1983 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 3)
  - Lobbying Assignments--Assembly, 1978 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 4)
  - Lobbying Assignments--Senate, 1978 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 5)
  - Lobbying Laws--Revisions, 1977, 1979-1980 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 6)
  - Lobbying Reform, 1977 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 7)
  - Lobbying Registration and Periodic Reports for NYSCC, 1977-1978 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 8)
  - Lobbying Registration and Periodic Reports for NYSCC, 1978 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 9)
  - Lobbying Registration and Periodic Reports for NYSCC, 1980 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 10)
  - Lobbying Registration and Periodic Reports for NYSCC, 1981 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 11)
  - Lobbying Registration and Periodic Reports for NYSCC, 1982 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 12)
  - Lobbying Registration and Periodic Reports for NYSCC, 1983 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 13)
  - Lobbying Registration and Periodic Reports for NYSCC, 1984-1986 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 14)
  - Lobbying Registration and Periodic Reports for NYSCC, 1985 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 15)
  - New York Temporary State Commission on Lobbying--1983 Annual Report, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 16)
  - New York Temporary State Commission on Lobbying--Correspondence, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 17)
  - New York Temporary State Commission on Lobbying-- Meeting Minutes, Annual Report and Correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 18)
  - New York Temporary State Commission on Regulation of Lobbying--Meeting Minutes, 1978-1981 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 19)
  - Public Financing Visits, 1979-1980 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 20)
  - A Report on Lobbying by State of California Fair Political Practices Commission, 1980 (Box 7 (3-Lobbying Files), Folder 21)
- OUTS Files (Open Up The System), 1976-1980; 4; 0.5 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically
  This series includes questionnaires used to survey state senators and assemblypersons as well as defeated candidates to ascertain their views on issues such as campaign funding, tax reform, broadcasting regulations, the bottle bill, the cost of education, legislative reform, PAC regulation, lobbying reform, conflict of interest in the legislature, and the public financing of campaigns. These files also include tabulations of these surveys which NYSCC used to map out strategy.
  - Legislative Questionnaires (Folder 1), 1976 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 22)
  - Legislative Questionnaires (Folder 2), 1976 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 23)
  - Legislative Questionnaires (Folder 3), 1976 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 24)
  - Legislative Questionnaires--Assembly, 1980 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 25)
  - Legislative Questionnaires--Senate, 1980 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 26)
  - Legislative Survey (Folder 1), 1977-1978 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 27)
  - Legislative Survey (Folder 2), 1977-1978 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 28)
  - Questionnaires for Candidates for U.S. House of Representatives, 1980 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 29)
  - Results for 1980 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 30)
  - Sample Questionnaires for 1978 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 31)
  - Sample Questionnaires and Results for 1972, 1974 and 1976 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 32)
  - Sample Questionnaires and Results for 1974 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 33)
  - Sample Questionnaires and Results for 1976 and 1978 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 34)
  - Sample Questionnaires and Results for 1978 (Folder 1), 1977-1978 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 35)
  - Sample Questionnaires and Results for 1978 (Folder 2), 1977-1978 (Box 7 (4-OUTS Files (Open Up The System)), Folder 36)